Association for Research and Enlightenment Collection
The Edgar Cayce Foundation
- Publications, 1931 2015
  - Box 2
    - A.R.E. Bulletin, 1947; Folder 2:3; Reilly, Harold J.; Turner, Gladys Davis; Cerminara, Gina; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Chandler, Julia; George, Henry, III; Cayce, Edgar; Bidwell, William Thomas; Cooley, Eleanor Strother; January -My Experience with the Physical Readings of Edgar Cayce -Readings on Problems of the Mind and Soul February -Chart of an Epileptic (Eleanor Strother Cooley) -From the Records -Of Interest to Members March -The Lost Continent of Atlantis -Of Interest to Members: Lectures -Books -Value of Astrological Text-Books (Rev. H.A. Norman) -From a Reading April -Growing Up Under a Cayce Reading (No. 415) -The Books of Geraldine Cummins on Perceptive Healing and Ultra-Perception as reviewed by Estella DeFord Graham -Congress Time -Your Blood May -Your Psychic Experiences -Books -Book Briefs June -Statements of Purpose -On the Records July -What Do the Cayce Readings Offer the Average Church Member? (Sartell Prentice) -Announcement [letters from ministers in answer to above] -Books -New Booklet [Eat to Live] August -Divine Guidance (Charles R. Wakeling, M.D., D.O.) -Ready for Questions -Of Interest to Members: Lectures September -Mind the Builder (William Thomas Bidwell, N.D., D.C.) -Ready for Questions: Karma and Family Antagonisms -First the Individual (Edgar Cayce) October -The Association's Health Service (Henry George III, M.D., D.O.) -Dreams November -Personal Memories of Edgar Cayce (Julia Chandler) -In Jesus' Time December -A Disciple of Christ in Our Day
    - A.R.E. Bulletin, 1948; Folder 2:4; Turner, Gladys Davis; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Bro, Harmon; Schwenger, Bertha Katrina; Reilly, Harold J.; Lavrischeff, Eloise; January -Serve the Lord (Carl A. Zapffe, M.S., Sc.D.) -Books February -A Psychic's Dreams -Books March -A Brief Report On A Psychological Experiment Carried On Through The Cooperation of Mrs. Eileen Garrett and Mr. Edgar Cayce -Books April / May -Of Transcending Time, Space and Matter -Search and Research -Books June -Edgar Cayce As A Religious Figure (Harmon H. Bro) -Books July -Exercise In A 3-Dimensional World (Bertha Katrina Schwenger) August -Healing Begins in the Mind -Books September -The Path of a Seeker (Eloise Lavrischeff) -The Cayce Readings and Religious Tradition (Harmon H. Bro)
    - A.R.E. Bulletin, 1958; Folder 2:5
    - A.R.E. Bulletin, 1959; Folder 2:6
    - A.R.E. Bulletin, 1960; Folder 2:7
    - A.R.E. Bulletin, 1961; Folder 2:8
    - A.R.E. Bulletin, 1962; Folder 2:9
    - A.R.E. Bulletin, 1963; Folder 2:10
    - A.R.E. Bulletin, 1964; Folder 2:11
    - A.R.E. Bulletin, 1965; Folder 2:12
  - Box 3
    - articles [Edgar Cayce] reprints, 1961 1975; Folder 3:1; Turner, Gladys Davis; Schroeder, Helen Ruth; Cayce, Edgar; Edgar and Gertrude Cayce as I Knew Them [Gladys Davis Turner] Your Personal Reading from the Edgar Cayce Readings [Helen Ruth Schroeder] Two Talks by Edgar Cayce - The Visible and the Invisible; The Second Coming
    - articles [health] reprints, 1971; Folder 3:2; Reilly, Harold J.; Schwenger, Bertha Katrina; Turner, Gladys Davis; O'Malley, George; Rudnikoff, Peter; Haller, Genevieve; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; The Physical Body is the Result [Harold J. Reilly] Exercise in a Three-Dimensional World [Bertha Katrina Schwenger] Chiropractic from the Edgar Cayce Records [Gladys Davis Turner] Healing Begins in the Mind [Harold J. Reilly] Castor Oil Pack Therapy - A Report [George O'Malley; Peter Rudnikoff] Alkaline-Acid Balance [Genevieve Haller] Health Hints from the Edgar Cayce Records [Hugh Lynn Cayce] Sleep Readings The Power of Attitudes in Serious Diseases [Gladys Davis Turner]
    - articles [metaphysics] reprints, 1950 1978; Folder 3:3; Turner, Gladys Davis; McArthur, Bruce; Estep, Florence; Cerminara, Gina; Gray, Lydia Schrader; Steinberger, Phyllis; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Taylor, Ariel Ivon; Stevenson, Ian; Meditation Reincarnation [Gladys Davis Turner] New Portrait of Our Planet and the Cayce Predictions [A Geologist] Planetary Sojourns [Gladys Davis Turner] The Knowledge that Life is Continuous Universal Laws [Bruce McArthur] How Astrology Can Help Us Understand Our Karma [Florence Estep] From the Candid Camera of the Cosmos [Gina Cerminara] Physical and Psychological Karma [Lydia Schrader Gray] Levels of Consciousness between Incarnations [Lydia Schrader Gray] Updating Earth Changes [anonymous] A Study of Color, Part 3 - Color, Symbology, and Aura Charts [Phyllis Steinberger] Oneness of All Force [Hugh Lynn Cayce] Books About Reincarnation (An Essay and an Annotated Book List) [Gina Cerminara] A Study of the Edgar Cayce Records on Life After Death [Hugh Lynn Cayce] Numerology - What the Edgar Cayce Readings Say About It [Ariel Ivon Taylor] Psychic Sources [Gladys Davis Turner] The Evidence for Survival from Claimed Memories of Former Incarnations [Ian Stevenson]
    - article [parapsychology] reprints, 1951; Folder 3:4; Petersen, William; An Experiment in Parapsychology
    - articles [psychology] reprints, 1949 1960; Folder 3:5; Shafer, Ruth M.; Schor, Robert; Clark, Tom C.; Elmore, Ellaine; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Gray, Lydia Schrader; To Those Who Teach [Ruth M. Shafer] The Meaning and Use of Dreams [FCB] The Ideal [Robert Schor] Jung's Psychology as a Background for Studying the Cayce Material [Tom C. Clark] Psychology for Parents in the New Age [Ellaine Elmore] The Mind of Man [Hugh Lynn Cayce] The Karma of Divorce [Lydia Schrader Gray] Child Training [Hugh Lynn Cayce]
    - articles [spirituality] reprints, 1951 1970; Folder 3:6; Cerminara, Gina; Clapp, Robert O.; Turner, Gladys Davis; Drummond, Richard; Nichols, Myrtle; Lambert, Margaret; Benesch, Samuel E.; Wynne, Esther; Krajenke, Robert; Robinson, Lytle; The Forgotten Virtue [Gina Cerminara] Living the Truth - How the A.R.E. Study Groups Apply the Lessons in A Search for God [Robert O. Clapp] Problems and their Solutions from the Edgar Cayce Readings [Gladys Davis Turner] The Way - Selections from the Edgar Cayce Readings [Gladys Davis Turner] The Appeal of Buddhism, Reconsidered [Richard H. Drummond] Life and Times of Jesus [Myrtle Nichols; Margaret Lambert] Plotinus [Samuel E. Benesch] Outlines and Excerpts on the Occult, the Mystic and the Christian based on the Edgar Cayce Readings [Esther Wynne] An Experiment in Bible Study: Part 1 [Robert Krajenke] The Resurrection - Selections from the Edgar Cayce Readings The Last Supper of Jesus with his Disciples - reading 5749-1 Reincarnation and the Scriptures [Lytle W. Robinson]
  - Box 4
    - The Searchlight, 1946 1948; Folder 4:1; Cerminara, Gina; Sugrue, Thomas; Elmore, Ellaine; Simmons, Riley; - He Is Your Brother! - Gina Cerminara -Where Are We Going? - Thomas Sugrue -Psychology for Parents in the New Age; Practice the Presence - Ellaine Elmore -The "Secret" of Edgar Cayce - Riley Simmons -Dreams and the Dreamers - Ellaine Elmore -The Christmas Message from the Readings of Edgar Cayce
    - The Searchlight, 1949; Folder 4:2; Turner, Gladys Davis; Lavrischeff, Eloise; Elmore, Ellaine; Cayce, Edgar Evans; Faus, Grace L.; Franco, Johan; Edmonds, Florence; Cayce, Edgar; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Ileana; Woodward, Mary Ann; LeNoir, Ruth; Reilly, Harold J.; Cerasco, Frank; Moore, Jennie; Shafer, Ruth M.; Cooley, Eleanor Strother; -Taking Stock of Ourselves - D. Gladys Turner -A Place for Peace: Dedication of Edgar Cayce's Study - Eloise Lavrischeff -Psychology for Parents in the New Age: Your Children Need Your Cooperation - Ellaine Elmore -The Current of Life - Edgar Evans Cayce -The Practical Application of Truth - Dr. Grace L. Faus -Psychology for Parents in the New Age: A Child is Entitled to His Own Reservations - Ellaine Elmore -Science Vs. The Readings on Arthritis - Johan Franco -Prayer and Meditation - Florence R. Edmonds -Psychology for Parents in the New Age: Utilize Your Child's Subconscious Mind -The Stream of Experience - Eloise Lavrischeff -The Meaning of Easter Today: Extracts from the Readings of Edgar Cayce -Psychology for Parents in the New Age: Plant Wisely; Reap in Joyous Abundance - Ellaine Elmore -Influences from Without - D. Gladys Davis and Eloise Lavrischeff -The Substance of Things - Dr. Grace L. Faus -Psychology for Parents in the New Age: If Freud Had Said "Social" Rather Than "Sex" - Ellaine Elmore -Continuity of Life - Edgar Cayce -Auras - Hugh Lynn Cayce -Earth's Missing Companion - Eloise Lavrischeff -Food: Our Helper on the Path to Attainment - Ileana -Meditation for Healing - Mary Ann Woodward -Twelve Steps in Soul Development (To be studied in parallel with the book, A Search for God) - Ruth LeNoir -The Book of Life - Eloise Lavrischeff -Changes in the Earth - D. Gladys Davis -Drugless Therapy from the Edgar Cayce Records - Harold J. Reilly -Group Study - Hugh Lynn Cayce -A Lady from North Carolina: A supplement for the September 15, 1949 Searchlight - Hugh Lynn Cayce -Searchlight Index -Dynamics of the Mind - Ellaine Elmore -Spiritual Signposts: Inspired by philosophical extracts from the Readings of Edgar Cayce - Frank Ceraso -His Own Country: A Prize Winning Essay in the Literary Contest at the Princess Anne County Fair - D. Gladys Davis -A Sweet Incense Before the Maker, The Creator - Jennie Moore -A Project for Members (selections from A Search for God) - Hugh Lynn Cayce -To Those Who Teach - Ruth M. Shafer -A Project for Members Part II (selections from A Search for God) - Hugh Lynn Cayce -The Drama of the Zodiac - Eleanor Strother Cooley
    - The Searchlight, 1950; Folder 4:3; DeGroot, A.J.; Cerasco, Frank; Cayce, Edgar; Green, S.N.; Franco, Johan; Franco, Eloise; Downey, Mary Elizabeth; Harcourt, Olive; Teltscher, Herry O.; George, Henry, III; Wynne, Esther; St. Clair, Mae Gimbert; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Turner, Gladys Davis; Bro, Harmon; Gray, Lydia Schrader; Pickard, George M.; Carter, Mary Ellen; Clark, Tom C.; -Christian Mysticism in Relation to Psychic Experience - Dr. A.T. DeGroot -Further Spiritual Signposts - Frank Cerasco -A Word from Mr. Cayce - Edgar Cayce -Science and Birthstones - S.N. Green -Mystery of Mysteries - Eloise and Johan Franco -The Great Pyramid Part I - Johan Franco -The Great Pyramid Part II - Johan Franco -The Great Pyramid Part III - Johan Franco -Easter Sunrise - Mary Elizabeth Downey -The Opposing Forces - Olive Harcourt -Psychographological Analysis of Edgar Cayce's Handwriting - Herry O. Teltscher -The Lions of Christian - Dr. Henry George, III -A Spiritual Signpost - Frank Cerasco -Home and Marriage - Esther Wynne and Mae Gimbert -Health Hints from the Edgar Cayce Records - Hugh Lynn Cayce -Expanding Consciousness through Reading - Mary Elizabeth Downey -Imagery or Reality? - D. Gladys Davis -The Seer and His Gift - Harmon Bro -The Karma of Divorce - Lydia J. Schrader Gray -Your Dreams: 1950 Congress Program -The Fountain of Youth - Eloise Franco -Why No Peace? - George M. Pickard -Prayer and Healing - Hugh Lynn Cayce -Chronology of the Life and Work of Edgar Cayce and the A.R.E. -Project X -The Doctrine of Reincarnation - Mary Ellen Carter -On Devotion - Frank Cerasco -Jung's Psychology as a Background for Studying the Cayce Material - Tom C. Clark
    - The Searchlight, 1951; Folder 4:4; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Petersen, William; Benesch, Samuel E.; Clark, Tom C.; Chandler, Julia; Miller, Noah; Cayce, Edgar; Cantley, Katherine; Gray, Lydia Schrader; -Project X: Reactions to Prayer and Meditation Periods - Hugh Lynn Cayce -Reincarnation and Karma: The Small Conference as a Way of Examining the Idea of Rebirth -Drawings with Lapis - William Petersen -Plotinus - Samuel E. Benesch -A Psychic Interprets His Dreams - Tom C. Clark -Outposts of Consciousness - Julia Chandler -Telepathy and Lapis Lingua - William N. Petersen -The Lost Continent of Atlantis - Hugh Lynn Cayce -An Example of Clairvoyance - Noah L. Miller -I Can Dream... - D. Gladys Davis -Present World Conditions - Edgar Cayce -The Gifts of Healing - Hugh Lynn Cayce -An Experiment in Parapsychology - William Petersen -Hope of the Future - Katherine Cantley -Our Judge and Jury - William Petersen -Our Judge and Jury Part II - William Petersen -A Way to Seek Truth - William Petersen -Edgar Cayce: The Man and his Work - Lydia J. Schrader Gray -750,000 Americans - Hugh Lynn Cayce -Children of the New Age: Based on 50 Life Readings for Children - Lydia J. Schrader Gray -Understanding Self: The Key to Spiritual Growth - Lydia J. Schrader Gray
    - The Searchlight, 1952; Folder 4:5; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Sugrue, Thomas; Robinson, Lytle; -A Study of the Edgar Cayce Records on Life after Death - Hugh Lynn Cayce -All Things to Your Remembrance - Hugh Lynn Cayce -The Mind of Man: A Study of the Edgar Cayce records on the nature and functions of mind - Hugh Lynn Cayce -American Mysticism, The Future of Religion in the United States - Thomas Sugrue -Reincarnation and the Scriptures - Lytle W. Robinson -Psychic Perception and Physiological Processes - Hugh Lynn Cayce -The Mystery of the Mayas - Lytle W. Robinson -Evidence of Past Lives: A Project for Members - Hugh Lynn Cayce
    - The Searchlight, 1953; Folder 4:6; Koernig, Ann; Gray, Lydia Schrader; Cooley, Eleanor Strother; Kahn, S. David; Robinson, Lytle; Cayce, Edgar Evans; Franco, Eloise; Miller, Shane; LeNoir, Ruth; Whitman Katherine; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Rusk, George Yeisley; -A Three-Way Analysis of an Individual's Potentials - Ann Koernig; Lydia J. Schrader Gray; Eleanor Strother Cooley; S. David Kahn -Physical and Psychological Karma - Lydia J. Schrader Gray -Delinquency - Juvenile or Parental? - Lytle W. Robinson -The Radio-active and Wet Cell Appliances - Edgar Evans Cayce -The Impact of a Life Reading - Lytle W. Robinson -The Valley of The Shadow - Eloise Franco -Where the Shoe Pinches: An Introduction to Economic Healing - Shane Miller -In His Presence: Personal Experiences During the Compilation of the Ninth Lesson of A Search for God - Ruth LeNoir -Spiritual Aspects of Healing: A Study Based on the Edgar Cayce Readings - Katherine Whitman -Analysis of Karma Questionnaires - Hugh Lynn Cayce -Karma, Science and Religion - George Yeisley Rusk
    - The Searchlight, 1954; Folder 4:7; Turner, Gladys Davis; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Cerminara, Gina; Reilly, Harold J.; Chandler, Julia; Miller, Shane; Walker, Eileen Margaret; -Practical Clairvoyance -Your Psychic Faculties: Selections from the Edgar Cayce Readings -How Long is Tomorrow? Selections from the Edgar Cayce Readings - Gladys Davis Turner -The Secret Place of the Most High - Hugh Lynn Cayce -The Candid Camera of the Cosmos - Gina Cerminara -The Forgotten Virtue - Gina Cerminara -The Physical Body is the Result - Harold J. Reilly -If I Should Die Tonight - Julia Chandler -Peace into the Bitter Place: Further Thoughts on the Law of Forgiveness - Shane Miller -Where Fear Enters... - Eileen Margaret Walker -Everyday Space-Travel - Eileen Margaret Walker -The Birth-Pattern of the Soul - Eileen Margaret Walker
    - The Searchlight, 1955; Folder 4:8; Carter, Mary Ellen; Baum, Betsey; Bro, Harmon; LeNoir, Ruth; Hewitt, Lynn E.; Ashlock, Renee; Franco, Eloise; Madigan, Jessica; Miller, Shane; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Wynne, Esther; George, Henry, III; -Line Upon Line -Use Your Bible -Why on Earth? - Mary Ellen Carter -Two Kinds of God - Betsey Baum -The Great Physician - Harmon Bro -The Home: Selections from the Edgar Cayce Readings - Ruth LeNoir -The Power of Imagination - Lynn E. Hewitt -The Destiny of the Body - Renee' Ashlock -Christ, the Amplifier - Eloise Franco -Love Your Teen-Ager! - Mary Ellen Carter -Your Karma is Your Opportunity - Jessica Madigan -Working with Dreams as Recommended by the Cayce Readings - Shane Miller -Who Am I? A Question Answered by An Edgar Cayce Reading - Hugh Lynn Cayce -Group Study: Suggestions from the Edgar Cayce Readings - Esther Wynne -The Soul's Record: Extracts from the Edgar Cayce Readings - Hugh Lynn Cayce -Thoughts for Thanksgiving: A Psychic Reading Through Edgar Cayce, November 20, 1938 -Psychic Findings in Epilepsy - Henry George III, D.O.
  - Box 4A
    - The Searchlight, 1956; Folder 4A:1; Shelton, Vaughan; Gammon, Margaret; Robinson, Lytle; Franco, Eloise; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Carter, Mary Ellen; Miller, Shane; Simmons, Riley; Schwenger, Bertha Katrina; Sechrist, Elsie; -The Cayce Story: Has it a Sequel? - Vaughan Shelton -Yes, We Have The Body - Margaret Gammon -The Return to Religion - Lytle W. Robinson -Mirror! Mirror! - Eloise Franco -Looking Forward - Hugh Lynn Cayce -The Earth is Changing - Mary Ellen Carter -Working with Dreams as Recommended by the Cayce Readings - Shane Miller -Citizen of the Universe - Hugh Lynn Cayce -The "Secret" of Edgar Cayce - Riley Simmons -Is Atomic Power Back? -Know It Is Speaking of Thee... - Mary Ellen Carter -Sleep and the Sixth Sense - Hugh Lynn Cayce -Group Study - Shane Miller -The Journey of Creative Thinking - Katrina Schwenger -Alfred Adler's "Individual Psychology": An Evaluation - Margaret H. Gammon -What Is Your Ideal?- Elsie Sechrist
    - The Searchlight, 1957; Folder 4A:2; Sugrue, Thomas; Gray, Lydia Schrader; Gammon, Margaret; Carter, Mary Ellen; Turner, Gladys Davis; Chandler, Julia; Whitman Katherine; Robinson, Lytle; McIntyre, Robert D.; -The New Tomorrow - Thomas Sugrue -Intellect and Intuition - Lydia Schrader Gray -Sleep From Sorrow and Wake With Elation - Margaret Gammon -The Golden Sceptre For All Ages: Easter Extracts compiled by Mary Ellen Carter -Planetary Sojourns: Selections from the Edgar Cayce Readings - Gladys Davis Turner -The Bible and You - Gladys Davis Turner -Levels of Consciousness Between Incarnations - Lydia Schrader Gray -The Body Is The Temple - Gladys Davis Turner -The Greater Awareness - Julia Chandler -The Panorama of Rebirth - Gladys Davis Turner -The Imprisoned Splendour - Katherine Whitman -The Law of Laws - Lytle W. Robinson -Clairvoyance: Action and Places: Selections from the Edgar Cayce Readings - Gladys Davis Turner -From Mystery to Meaning: A Methodist Minister Speaks His Mind - Rev. Robert D. McIntyre
    - The Searchlight, 1958; Folder 4A:3; Turner, Gladys Davis; Gammon, Margaret; Ashlock, Renee; Foster, Katharine; Clairmonte, Nell; Stanley, Dorothy Evelyn; Cayce, Edgar; Chandler, Julia; Carter, Mary Ellen; Robinson, Lytle; Turner, Albert E.; -Pharmacology in the Edgar Cayce Readings - Gladys Davis Turner; Margaret Gammon -Personal Application of Symbols Found in Archetypal Charts - Renee Ashlock -Where the Light Begins - Katharine Foster -That Ye Might Know Him Better: The Incarnations of Jesus - Nell Clairmonte -When Sorrow Comes: Help Found in The Edgar Cayce Readings - Dorothy Evelyn Stanley -What Is Truth? - Edgar Cayce -Man's Relationship to God - Edgar Cayce -Akashic Records: Historians of the Soul - Julia Chandler -Home Is The Pattern - Mary Ellen Carter -Some Aspects of The Law of Balance - Margaret Gammon -The Essenes and the Dead Sea Scrolls - Lytle W. Robinson -When Is A Man Educated? - Julia Chandler -Is Reincarnation In The Bible? - Albert E. Turner
    - The Searchlight, 1959; Folder 4A:4; Cayce, Edgar; Ballard, Juliet Brooke; Ballbusch, Peter; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Gammon, Margaret; Smock, Robert L.; Turner, Gladys Davis; Hotten, Mayo; Slater, Robert S.; -Two Talks By Edgar Cayce: The Aura; Fate -One Newly Dead; Rebirth - Juliet Brooke Ballard -The Secret of Happiness - Peter Ballbusch -The Language of the Unconscious -Hugh Lynn Cayce -Dangerous Doorways Into The Unconscious - Hugh Lynn Cayce -The Long Road - Juliet Brooke Ballard -Mind in Relation to Healing: Two Talks By Edgar Cayce -A Life Reading 20 Years Later - Margaret Gammon -Where Do We Go From Here? - Robert L. Smock -The Power of Attitudes in Serious Diseases - Gladys Davis Turner -Atlantean Influence In The Arts - Juliet Brooke Ballard -Edgar Cayce, Osteopathy and The Fourth Dimension - Mayo L. Hotten, D.O. -The Essenes And The Christ Child - Rev. Robert S. Slater -Osteopathy from the Edgar Cayce Records - Gladys Davis Turner
    - The Searchlight, 1960; Folder 4A:5; Cayce, Edgar; Reilly, Harold J.; Turner, Albert E.; Mormon, Anna; Clapp, Robert O.; Price, Wym; Gammon, Margaret; Miller, Shane; Ballard, Juliet Brooke; Turner, Gladys Davis; Seay, Richmond; -Three Talks By Edgar Cayce: What Is a Reading?; Psychic Phenomena; The First Ten Minutes After Death -Healing Begins In the Mind - Harold J. Reilly -Latter Days in The Master's Ministry: Reflected in The Lives of Those Illuminated by His Teachings -Is Reincarnation in the Bible? Part II - Albert E. Turner -The A.R.E. Summer Camp For Children: Reports on the Younger Group - Anna Mormon, Bob Clapp, Wym Price -Drugless Therapy in the Edgar Cayce Records - Harold J. Reilly -Esoteric Astrology In The Edgar Cayce Readings - Margaret Gammon -The Bible As A Handbook For Understanding Oneself - Shane Miller -The Bible As A Handbook For Understanding Oneself: Part II - Shane Miller -The Bible As A Handbook For Understanding Oneself: Part III - Shane Miller -All Things Have Need Of Thee - Juliet Brooke Ballard -The Power of Attitudes in Serious Diseases: Part II, Arthritis - Gladys Davis Turner -Music, and What It May Mean To You - Richmond Seay
    - The Searchlight, 1961; Folder 4A:6; Cayce, Edgar; Turner, Gladys Davis; Ballard, Juliet Brooke; Clapp, Robert O.; O'Malley, George; Rudnikoff, Peter; Chandler, Julia; Miller, Shane; Estep, Florence; Spickler, Betty; -Two Talks By Edgar Cayce: The Visible and the Invisible; The Second Coming -Problems and Their Solutions from the Edgar Cayce Readings - Gladys Davis Turner -New Portrait of Our Planet and the Cayce Predictions - By a Geologist -Scillas - Juliet Brooke Ballard -Report On A.R.E. Summer Camp For Young People: 1960 Session - Robert Clapp -Castor Oil Pack Therapy: A Report - George O'Malley, D.O., Peter Rudnikoff, D.O. -New Lamps For Old - Julia Chandler -The Bible As a Handbook For Understanding Oneself, Part IV: Prophets and Priests - Shane Miller -The Bible As a Handbook For Understanding Oneself, Part V: The New Testament - Shane Miller -The Values and Dangers pf Hypnosis (By a Member of the Medical Profession) -How Astrology Can Help Us Understand Our Karma - Florence Estep -Random Journey Through The Readings - Betty Spickler
    - The Searchlight, 1962; Folder 4A:7; Cayce, Edgar; Miller, Shane; Ballard, Juliet Brooke; Carter, Mary Ellen; Turner, Gladys Davis; Adams, Frank; Cerminara, Gina; Turner, Albert E.; Cayce, Edgar Evans; Spickler, Betty; -Two Talks By Edgar Cayce: How to Develop Your Psychic Ability; Mental Telepathy -Emblem of the Heavenly Home - Juliet Brooke Ballard -One To The Other - Juliet Brooke Ballard -The Bible As A Handbook For Understanding Oneself, Part VI: The Book of Job - Shane Miller -The Church Invisible - Mary Ellen Carter -Chiropractic From The Edgar Cayce Records - Gladys Davis Turner -The Philosophy Within A Beatitude, Part I: 705,000 Days of Interpretation - Frank O. Adams -The Philosophy Within A Beatitude, Conclusion: A Bridge of Comprehension - Frank O. Adams -Books About Reincarnation - Gina Cerminara -Cry Not Peace, Peace: Based on the Edgar Cayce readings on the achievement of the New Order of Peace in the world, and the individual responsibility to this task - Albert E. Turner -On Speaking Terms! What the Edgar Cayce Readings said about what we say, and a report from nine people who tried to watch what they said for 24 hours.. - Mary Ellen Carter -The A.R.E. Research Program, Part I: The Physical Readings - Edgar Evans Cayce -Harvest of Harmony - Betty Spickler